nirdeshak.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Nirdeshak

Nirdeshak.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer’s personal information. This statement applies with respect to the information that we collect from the Company Web site, located at [www.nirdeshak.com](http://www.nirdeshak.com/). Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

**I. INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways. We may also ask you to provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your age, name etc. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a survey or registration form. The types of information that may be requested include your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

**II. USE OF INFORMATION**

In general, we will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided. We may also use this information to deliver to you information about our company and promotional material of some of our new initiatives. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings from Nirdeshak.com. Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in.

**III. USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

**IV. USE OF COOKIES**

When you view our Web site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a ‘cookie’ or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Web site as easily as possible. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection.

**V. SECURITY**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as ‘perfect security’ on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.

**VI. OTHER WEB SITES**

Our Web site contains links to other Web sites. Nirdeshak.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**VII. UPDATE INFORMATION**

Nirdeshak.com allows its users the option to change or modify information previously provided. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from or corrected in our records.

**VIII. OPT OUT CHOICE**

You may opt-out of using our services at any time by deleting your account and please follow the appropriate instructions for the same.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [contact@nirdeshak.com](mailto:contact@nirdeshak.com)
